生日快乐,宝贝。
Happy birthday, baby.
对不起,我迟到了。我的歉意。
Sorry I'm late. My apologies.
不用担心。我不会耽误你太久的。
No worries. I won't keep you long.
我要准备一份证词，我知道今天是你妻子的生日。
I have a deposition to prepare, and I understand that today was your wife's birthday.
是,是的。
It is, yeah.
我不喜欢把你从回忆中拉出来，但我相信你明白有些对话最好是面对面的。
I do not enjoy pulling you away from your remembrances, but I'm sure you understand that some conversations are best had in person.
你确定你的助手准备好了吗?
Now, you're sure your associate is prepared to do this thing?
他是。
He is.
因为结果必须是决定性的。
Because the results need to be definitive.
这将是。
It will be.
至于路易斯，我们的意图很明确吗?
And where Luis is concerned, our intentions are clear?
- - - - - -晶体。——好。
- Crystal. - Good.
和俄罗斯人的交易太重要了不能让路易斯·贝拉斯克斯妨碍。
This deal with the Russians is too important to let Luis Velasquez get in the way.
阿诺德得快点了。
Arnold will need to make haste.
因为他们想在今天下班前把现金存入我的办公室。
Because they want a cash deposit in my office by the close of business today.
不是一个问题。
Not a problem.
很好。
Very well.
向前,向上。
Onwards and upwards.
祝你玩得愉快。
Have a good one.
嘿,冲突。
Hey, Carlito.
搜索的借口。我有，信任问题。
Excuse the search. I got, uh, trust issues.
我甚至不相信自己。
I don't even trust myself.
你理解。
You understand.
我明白了。
I understand.
喂，小伙子，给他带点…一些,嗯,龙舌兰酒。
Yo, corrier, bring him some, uh... some, uh, tequila.
——如果?——没有。
- Sí? - No.
我知道你只是公事公办。
I know you're strictly business.
让我给你一些信息，也许能救你一命。
Let me bless you with information that might save your life.
这里的人不会相信你的。
They're never gonna trust you here.
对阿诺德·所罗门这样的人来说，你就是个小豆子。
To people like Arnold Solomon, you're just another fucking beaner.
就在你最需要他们的时候，他们却因为不喜欢你而把你推到车底下。
Just when you need them the most, they'll throw you under the bus because they don't like you.
还有Entiendes ?
¿Entiendes?
我是路易斯·维拉斯。
I'm Luis Velasquez.
我受到全世界的爱戴和尊敬。
I'm loved and respected worldwide.
你也可以。
And you can be, too.
鉴于俄罗斯的威胁，所罗门先生认为让我们做你的合作伙伴是一种保险。
You see, in light of the Russian threat, Mr. Solomon thought that having us as your partner would be a form of insurance.
唷，这家伙要杀了我。
Yo, this guy kills me, man.
你是认真的吗?
Are you serious?
你给我穿上"灵魂列车"的鞋子滚出去。
You take those "Soul Train" shoes and get the fuck out of here.
你站到铁轨那边去。
You stay your side of the tracks.
我会坚持我的。你明白吗?
I'll stay on mine. You understand?
-谈判结束了?——走吧。
- End of negotiations, then? - Go.
“谈判的终结。”
"End of negotiations."
你他妈有什么毛病?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
我真该让赫克托踢你的屁股。
I should have fucking Hector just kick you in the ass.
我不需要你或者他妈的阿诺德·所罗门来对付俄国人。
I don't need you or Arnold fucking Solomon to deal with the Russians.
如果……如果所罗门先生提高报价呢?
What if... What if Mr. Solomon raised his offer?
让我想想。
Let me think about that.
所罗门操。
Fuck Solomon.
嘿!
Hey!
不到的。
Carlito.
啊!哦!
Ah! Oh!
昨天的比赛太精彩了。
That was a hell of a game yesterday.
我的意思是，胜利并不是一切，但它比第二名强多了。
I mean, winning isn't everything, but it beats the hell out of coming in second.
你不喜欢你的家乡的足球，是吗?
You don't care for football where you come from, do you?
不，我猜你们都是冰球迷。
Nah, you're all hockey crazy, I bet.
你确定就是这个?
You sure this is it?
好像是我会计的大楼。
Looks like my accountant's building.
我的线人拿假释听证会打赌。
My CI has wagered a parole hearing on it.
我们很好。
We're good.
今晚有什么好事吗?
So, doing anything nice tonight?
给我留下了深刻的印象,侦探。
I'm impressed, Detective.
是我手机上的提醒。
It was an alert on my phone.
生日快乐。
Happy birthday.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
宿醉可不能把它吓跑，弗林。
Can't scare it away with a hangover, Flynn.
我很好。
I'm fine.
那个西装革履的家伙是谁?
Who the hell is the slick suit?
一个明显不是雅利安人的顾客脖子上有党卫军纹身。
SS neck tattoo on a distinctly non-Aryan-looking customer.
海军陆战队狙击手用这个纹身。
Marine snipers use that tattoo.
他们不应该这么做，但侦察兵狙击手倾向于制定自己的规则。
They're not supposed to, but Scout Snipers tend to make their own rules.
真的吗?
Really?
听起来像我认识的另一个人。
Sounds like someone else I know.
咬我,Koschek。
Bite me, Koschek.
做梦吧，硬汉。
In your dreams, tough guy.
看着他。
Look at him.
我应该查查他的车牌。
I should run his plate.
他妈的。
Fuck.
微笑,只小猪。
Smile, little piggy.
是他逼我们的。
He fucking made us.
我要把他带回来。
I'm bringing him in.
看我的鼻子。
Look at my nose.
一切都查清楚了，警探。
Everything checks out, Detective.
你可以走了。
You're free to go.
谢谢。
Thanks.
邻居们什么也没看见。
Neighbors didn't see anything.
除了我们看到的和没看到的，什么都没有。
Nothing to go on other than what we saw or didn't see.
我们是愚蠢的。
We were stupid.
应该跟踪他的。
Should have tailed him.
哦,天啊。
Oh, geez.
——哦,耶稣。-是的。
- Oh, Jesus. - Yeah.
这太疯狂了，科斯切克。
This is some crazy shit, Koschek.
糟糕的一天。
Hell of a day.
就像狂欢节后的波旁街。
Like Bourbon Street after Mardi Gras.
好吧，派对结束了。
Yeah, well, the party's over.
我和戴利要接手了
Me and Daley are taking over.
队长想让你们俩回家。
Captain wants you two to go home.
什么?
What?
这是他妈的扯淡。这是我们的案子。
That's fucking bullshit. This is our case.
-慢着，慢着，冷静点。-回拨，富林。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, down, girl. - Dial it back, Flynn.
你刚才说什么?
What did you just say?
我们只是听从警监的命令，好吗?
Hey, we're just following Captain's orders, alright?
但我们看到嫌犯了。
But we had eyes on the suspect.
然后你让他跑了，一切都乱套了。
And then you let him get away and all hell broke loose.
好吧?
Okay?
不值得。
It's not worth it.
螺丝你,尼尔。
Screw you, Lanier.
♬我向上帝祈祷我从来没有出生过
♪ I wish to the Lord I had never had been born ♪
♬我的眼睛从来没有照过你和你的肉体
♪ Never shone my eyes upon the flesh of you and yours ♪
♪再也没有爱过，我的爱人再也没有爱过
♪ Never have to love again, my lover loves no more ♪
♪我做了一点关于太阳落山的♪
♪ I made a little bit on the falling of the sun ♪
♪曾经有过那个阳光明媚的日子
♪ That sunny day was had ♪
现在我的比赛快结束了
♪ And now my race is nearly run ♪
♬相信我的话吧，亲爱的主，在我的时间结束之前
♪ Take me on my word, dear Lord, before my time is done ♪
嘿。
Hey.
他准备好见你们了。
He's ready to see y'all now.
这个案子归福利特管
The case goes to Follett.
他知道该怎么做。
He'll know what to do.
卡洛对待委拉斯开兹就像对待冰冷的职业球员一样。
Carlo handled Velasquez like an ice-cold pro.
他不想谈判，所以你的口信已经传达了。
He didn't want to negotiate, so your message has been delivered.
你不能说我没试过。
Well, you can't say I didn't try.
告诉他。
Tell him.
两种可能的目击者。
Two possible witnesses.
他们是警察。
They were cops.
他们能把这次袭击和你联系起来吗?
Can they tie the hit to you?
还是你对我?
Or you to me?
不，他们可能在监视委拉斯开兹。
No, they were probably staking out Velasquez.
我是说，纯粹的巧合。
I mean, pure coincidence.
这是你的错。
This is your fault.
——我知道。-你应该去的。
- I know. - You should have been there.
他会解决这个问题。
He'll fix this.
在很多方面，卡洛在这方面都比我强。
In many ways, Carlo is better at this stuff than I am.
-这是你的烂摊子。-你来打扫。
- This is your mess. - You clean it up.
给你48小时。
You got 48 hours.
就当我做了吧，先生。
Consider it done, sir.
你最好。
You better.
我们需要地址。
We need addresses.
正确的。
Right.
我在来的路上给部门联系人打了电话。
Yeah, I called my department contact on the way here.
我只是在等他破解他们的文件。
I'm just waiting for him to crack open their files.
然后我们好。
Then we're good.
我拍到了他们的车牌号，应该很快就能搞定了。
I got a picture of their license plate, so it should be a done deal in no time.
好,好。
Good, good.
我得把这破玩意交给福利特。
I got to get this shit over to Follett.
那我来帮你完成。
Then I'll help you finish up.
我想俄国人会很高兴墨西哥人被除掉的。
I think the Russians will be happy with the Mexican out of the way.
很好。艾丽卡。
Very well. Erica.
随着这笔交易的成功完成，阿诺德将成为一个非常有权势的人。
With the successful conclusion of this deal, Arnold is going to become an extraordinarily powerful man.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
房地产不是我的菜。
Real estate's never been my thing.
是的,太糟糕了。
Yeah, too bad.
委拉斯开兹应该知道不要跟他合作。
Velasquez should have known don't go along with him.
你了解古希腊人吗，盖比?
Do you know much about the ancient Greeks, Gabe?
嗯，他们非常重视他们的自由。
Well, they valued their liberty highly.
希腊人鼓励一种自力更生的个人主义。
The Greeks encouraged a kind of self-reliant individualism.
当时没有法律可言，所以警察也就没必要了。
There were no laws to speak of, so police weren't necessary.
听起来像是我喜欢的地方。
Sounds like my kind of place.
但古希腊人在偷窃或抢劫方面是划清界限的。
But the ancient Greeks drew a line in the sand when it came to stealing or robbery.
他们不喜欢牛被偷，也不喜欢人家被破门而入。
They did not like their cattle being stolen and they did not like their homes being broken into.
但是没有警察，他们怎么找到罪犯呢?
But with no police, how would they find the culprit?
事实上，他们有各种各样的方法来判定有罪。
Actually, they had various methods to determine guilt.
其中一项行动涉及围捕12名嫌疑人。
One of them involved rounding up 12 suspects.
法官会给这些嫌疑人每人一根6英寸长的棍子，但他会告诉他们，小偷的棍子会在第二天早上多长一英寸。
And a judge would give each of those suspects a stick 6 inches long, but he would tell them that the thief's stick would grow an extra inch by the next morning.
通常，有罪的一方会咬下他的一英寸的棍子，然后第二天早上，他会在那里手里拿着5英寸的承认有罪的棍子。
Invariably, the guilty party would chew off one inch of his stick, and then the next morning, he would be there holding a 5-inch admission of guilt stick in his hand.
重点是，在我做辩护律师的30多年里，我知道了一个无可辩驳的事实，那就是罪犯最大的敌人是他们自己。
The point is, for the 30-something years that I've been a defense attorney, I have learned one irrefutable truth, and that is criminals are their own worst enemy.
我不能说我不同意你。
Can't say I disagree with you.
听着，我很感谢你的送餐。
Well, listen, I appreciate the delivery.
和弗拉德的交易会让大家赚很多钱。
And this deal with Vlad is gonna make everyone a lot of money.
阿诺德似乎是这么认为的。
Arnold seems to think so.
你不?
You don't?
我怎么想真的不重要。
It really doesn't matter what I think.
听。
Listen.
阿诺德信任你，信任是有价值的。
Arnold trusts you, and trust is a valuable commodity.
他相信你能在街上保护他，他相信我能照顾他的法律和经济利益。
He trusts you to protect him on the street, and he trusts me to look after his legal and financial interests.
在这方面，我们是相似的。
In that respect, we're alike.
我们认识有几年了，对吧，福利特先生?
We've known each other for a few years now, right, Mr. Follett?
你对我很好，我很感激。
You've been very kind to me, and I appreciate that.
但是…我们一点也不像。
But... we are nothing alike.
你到达。
You're reaching.
来吧,现在。
Come on, now.
呼吸。
Breathe.
你不能再这样下去了。
You can't keep going on like this.
愤怒会吞噬你直到你一无所有。
The anger's gonna eat away at you until there's nothing left.
——我知道。-在阿富汗，我们都经历了一些非常糟糕的事情。
- I know. - In Afghanistan, we both lived through some really bad things.
但你在沙坑里可是个冷酷的专业人士。
But you were a cold professional back in the sandbox.
你头脑清醒的时候还是这样。
You still are when your head's on straight.
但你似乎下定决心不想好起来。
But you seem determined not to want to get any better.
你觉得我应该去找个高薪的心理医生吐露心声吗?
Think I should go to some overpaid shrink and spill my guts?
不能伤害。
Couldn't hurt.
至少，你可以保住你的事业。
At the very least, you might save your career.
我已经知道我是怎么了。
I already know what's wrong with me.
每次我遇到一个人，我都会不由自主地想到杀死他们最好最有效的方法。
Every time I meet someone, I automatically think about the best and most efficient way to kill them.
我再也关不掉它了。
I can't switch it off anymore.
我们都经历过你现在的处境。
We've all been where you're at.
你要学会把外面的一切都抛在脑后。
You just got to learn to leave the outside outside.
我要上课。
I got a class.
如果你需要什么，尽管来找我。
You need anything, you know where to find me.
哟,小伙子。那就这样吧。那就这样吧。
Yo, guys. There you go. There you go.
的家伙……兰斯·科斯切克警探，52岁。
That's the guy... Detective Lance Koscheck, 52.
过去的他。
Past his prime.
看着他。真是悲惨的生活。
Look at him. What a sad fucking life.
没有家人，叫外卖，一个人吃。
No family, orders takeout, eats it alone.
我的内线说他和他的搭档今天早上被踢出了这个案子，所以…让我们把她搞定。
My inside guy said that he and his partner got booted off the case this morning, so... Let's get her done.
好吧。
Okay.
嘿,兄弟。
Hey, brother.
很抱歉打扰你，但我让你分心了。
I'm sorry to disturb you, but I'm the distraction.
你他妈在说什么，混蛋?
What the fuck are you talking about, asshole?
任何时候。
Anytime.
哦，主啊，你知道我有
♪ Oh, Lord, you know I have ♪
♪没有你这样的朋友♪
♪ No other friend like you ♪
♪如果天堂不是我的家
♪ If heaven's not my home ♪
哦,男人。要下雨了。
Oh, man. It's gonna rain.
我骨子里都能感觉到。
I can feel it in my bones.
♪……所有的一切都在向我招手
♪ ...all have beckoned me ♪
变老真烦人。
Getting old's a bitch.
我的兄弟姐妹们
♪ My brothers and my sisters ♪
♪在那片光荣的土地上♪
♪ Over in that glory land ♪
♬我不指望退出
♪ I don't expect to quit ♪
哦，看那该死的东西。
Oh, look at that shit.
你到底帮不帮?
You gonna help or what?
不，老实说，你一个人做得很好。
No, honestly, you're doing very well on your own.
♪……♪有家的感觉
♪ ...feel at home ♪
♪在这个世界上♪
♪ In this world anymore ♪
你妻子问过你的工作吗?
Does your wife ever ask about your job?
对信任你的人撒谎很容易。
It's easy to lie to someone who trusts you.
半真半假不是谎言。
Half truths aren't lies.
你一直这么对自己说。
You keep telling yourself that.
我很钦佩你，你知道吗，像你一样花时间在她的墓前。
I admire you, you know, spending time at her grave like you do.
我喜欢那里。
I like it there.
总有一天，我可能要多待一会儿。
One day, I'll probably have to stay longer.
曾经希望我们可以做不同的事情吗?
Ever wish we could have done things differently?
现在又有什么关系呢?
What's it matter now?
我训练你来接替我多久了?
How long have I been training you to be my replacement?
美好的两个月。
Two wonderful months.
别让阿诺德晃你，好吗?
Don't let Arnold shake you, okay?
我走的时候，你要像我一样。
When I go, just act like me.
假以时日，他会信任你的。
In time, he'll trust you.
我希望。
I hope.
我真的希望这份工作能给我尊重，你知道吗?
I really want the respect that comes with this job, you know?
这他妈的有什么意义?
What's the fucking point?
另一个证人呢?
What about the other witness?
别担心。
Don't worry about it.
这是我的混乱。我来打扫。
It's my mess. I'll clean it up.
你确定吗?
You sure about this?
你知道这对阿诺德有多重要。
You know how important this is to Arnold.
我想到了几个击球手，所以我们会处理的。
I got a few hitters in mind, so we'll take care of it.
你应该回家。这是亚历克斯的一天。
You should go home. It's Alex's day.
是的。听着，我很感激。
Yeah. Look, I appreciate that.
顺便说一句，你从这份工作中得到的，不是尊重。
By the way, what you get from this job, it ain't respect.
是恐惧。
It's fear.
它总是恐惧。
It's always fear.
记住这一点。
Remember that.
生日快乐,宝贝。
Happy birthday, baby.
我每天都在想你。
I miss you every day.
♬瓶塞盖好了，地板上蜡了
♪ The corks are capped, the floors are being waxed ♪
我知道时间已经过去了
♪ I know the moment's passed ♪
♪大家都走了，我就要被车碾了
♪ And everyone has left and I'm about to be run over ♪
♪但我似乎无法唤醒自己
♪ But I can't quite seem to wake myself ♪
♬两个世界碰撞，我在睡梦中起舞
♪ Both worlds collide, I'm dancing in my sleep ♪
拉尼尔，韦伯，到前面来。
Lanier, Webber, to the front.
你和我在一起。
You're with me.
不要退缩。
Do not hold back.
让我们终结这个贱人。
Let's terminate this bitch.
走了。
Go.
你是谁? !你想要什么?
Who are you?! What do you want?!
哦!
Oh!
等等,停下来,弗林!
Wait, stop, Flynn!
是我!尼尔,阻止它!
It's me! Lanier, stop it!
狗屎,拉尼尔?
Shit, Lanier?
Mierda。
Mierda.
他妈的。
Fuck.
是的。有什么事吗?
Yeah. What's up?
我们这里出了点状况。
We have a situation here.
——Ay-yi-yi。-我带走的那三个人都死了。
- Ay-yi-yi. - The three guys I took are dead.
——她还活着。你是认真的吗?
- She's alive. - Are you serious?
我知道。我知道。这是他妈的狗屎。
I know. I know. It's fuckin' shit.
我们混乱的。
We fucked up.
好吧。我叫阿诺。
Okay. I'll call Arnold.
阿诺德现在可以见你了。
Arnold will see you now.
留下来。他不想见你。
Stay. He don't want to see you.
你他妈开什么玩笑?
Are you fucking kidding me?
早上好,先生。
Morning, sir.
你觉得我需要听俄国人说这些废话吗?
You think I need to hear this shit from the Russian?
对不起。我们正在处理这件事。
Sorry. It's being taken care of.
一枪爆了这贱人的头。
Put a bullet in this bitch's head.
不然我就放你一枪。
Or I'll put one in yours.
就像我说的，已经在处理了。
Like I said, it's being taken care of.
我觉得你应该重新考虑一下最后那句话。
And I think you should rethink those last few words.
他们在侮辱我们两个人。
They're insulting to both of us.
是的。好吧。我很抱歉。
Yeah. Alright. I'm sorry.
你知道我的嘴。
You know my mouth.
除掉那个警察。
Just get rid of the cop.
它会做的。
It'll be done.
不用担心。
No worries.
我向你保证。
You have my word.
以后。
Later.
我们走吧。
Let's get out of here.
耶稣基督!
Jesus Christ!
吓死我了，弗林。
Scared the crap out of me, Flynn.
-你好吗?-你好吗?
- How are you? - How are you?
告诉我你知道昨天贝拉斯克斯被杀的事。
Tell me what you know about the Velasquez hit yesterday.
——忘记委拉斯开兹。-告诉我你去哪了?
- Forget Velasquez. - Tell me where you been?
我们在你家发现了机枪，三具尸体，还有一堆废黄铜。
We found machine guns, three very deceased John Does, and a stack of spent brass at your house.
-三个约翰?-是的。三。
- Three John Does? - Yeah. Three.
草坪上的一个看起来像是被人用绞肉机绞过的。
One on the lawn looked like he'd been put through a meat grinder.
没有牙科记录，没有指纹。
No dental records, no prints.
在草坪上的是拉尼尔。
Guy on the lawn was Lanier.
哦,胡说。
Oh, bullshit.
这是他。
It was him.
你知道吗?
Did you know?
-不，不，他妈的不，瓦内萨-你知道吗?
- No, no, fuck no, Vanessa. - Did you know?
-当然不是。-你是他的搭档
- Of course not. - You're his partner.
你他妈也有份。
You're fucking in on this, too.
我是他的搭档，但我没跟他结婚。
Yeah, I'm his partner, but I'm not married to the guy.
如果他是脏的，那跟我一点关系都没有。
If he's dirty, it's got nothing to do with me.
他们有我的家庭住址，戴利。
They had my home address, Daley.
我不知道。我发誓。
I didn't know. I swear.
有人收到Koschek的消息吗?
Has anyone heard from Koschek?
不。
No.
听着，你需要进来。对吧?
Look, you need to come in. Alright?
队长今天早上大发脾气。
Captain's pitching a shit fit this morning.
她要给你发通缉令了。
She's about to issue a BOLO for you.
我觉得我还是待在外面比较好。
I think I'm better out here for now.
你疯了,现在。看起来……我们就一起进去。
You're crazy, now. Look... we'll just go in together.
我们直接坐车去分局就行。
We'll just ride right over to the precinct.
听着，你得找到科斯切克。
Listen, you got to find Koschek.
把他送到安全的地方。
Put him in a safe house.
如果这家伙来找我，他可能也在追杀科舍克。
If this guy came for me, he's probably gunning for Koschek, too.
他杀了委拉斯开兹，现在他来找目击者。
He killed Velasquez, now he's coming for the witnesses.
那你一定要进来。
Then you definitely need to come in.
我得挂了，戴利。
I got to go, Daley.
你要去哪，瓦内萨?
Where you going, Vanessa?
你知道那里对我不安全。
You know it isn't safe for me.
什么叫它不是…凡妮莎!
What do you mean it's not... Vanessa!
是吗?
Yeah?
你终于决定回我电话了，混蛋。
You finally decide to return my call, you fucking asshole.
是你杀了拉尼尔吗?你杀了我的搭档吗?
Did you kill Lanier? Did you kill my partner?
原谅我吗?
Excuse me?
不，不，不。我问，你回答。
No, no, no, no. I ask, and you answer.
明白了吗?
Get it?
她在哪里呢?
Where is she?
她在逃亡。
She's on the run.
现在,倾听。
Now, listen.
你的整个计划就是害死好警察。
This whole plan of yours is getting good cops killed.
你要把我弄哭了。
You're going to make me cry.
听着，我要出去!
Listen, I want out!
-外面没有。-你想退出?
- There's no out here. - You want out?
你去给自己买个刀片割破你的肥手腕，你个黑警察。
You go buy yourself a fucking razor blade and cut your fat fucking wrist, you dirty cop.
我什么也没听到。
I hear nothing.
所以你去找她。
So you find her.
给我一个地址。
Get me an address.
不然我就去拜访你。
Or I'll pay you a visit.
他妈的!他妈的!他妈的!他妈的!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
我们肯定低估了她。
We definitely underestimated her.
她是训练有素。
She's well trained.
戴利把她的档案发给我了。
Daley's sending me her file, actually.
他是另一个没解决的问题，你知道吗?
He's another loose end, you know?
他对电脑很在行。他很聪明。
He's good with computers. He's smart.
最重要的是，他怕我。
Best thing of all, he's scared of me.
-我是认真的
- Mm. - I'm serious.
他吓坏了。我说什么他就做什么。
He's terrified. He'll do anything I say.
现在。
For now.
一旦他不再是线人，他就成了幽灵，所以…对了，我们需要有人克隆弗林的手机这样她接电话时我们就能追踪到她。
As soon as he ceases to be an asset, he's a ghost, so... By the way, we need someone to clone Flynn's phone so we can trace her when she answers.
你有别人吗?
You got someone?
我不知道，但阿诺德知道。
I don't, but Arnold does.
我会给他打电话的。
I'll give him a call.
-小姐-好吧
- Miss. - Alright.
喂?
Hello?
沃尔特?
Walter?
哦,沃尔特。
Oh, Walter.
他妈的。
Fuck.
我得跟你谈谈。这很重要。
Hey, I need to talk to you. It's important.
我需要你的帮助。
I need your help.
当然可以。任何东西。
Of course. Anything.
我需要你帮我搞到一个人的信息。
I need you to get me some info on someone.
谁是那个幸运的家伙?
Who's the lucky guy?
呃,侦察狙击。
Uh, Scout Sniper.
我想他是本地人。
I think he's local.
拉把椅子过来。看看这是什么。
Pull up a chair here. See what we got here.
在我们的数据库里找不到任何东西。
Can't find anything on our database.
-那家伙就是个鬼。-你很幸运，我的数据库是从警局没查到的地方开始。
- Guy's a damn ghost. - Lucky for you, my database starts where the P.D. leaves off.
等待。这是他。
Wait. That's him.
侦察兵狙击课程让这样的人做一些我们大多数人都难以接受的事情。
Scout Sniper courses takes men like this and teaches them to do things that most of us would find difficult to stomach.
有些人就是擅长杀人。
Some men are just good at killing.
小维，如果你想让我深入调查，我得知道，我们的紧急程度是多少?
Yo, V, if you want me dig in deeper, I need to know, what's our level of emergency?
他昨晚杀了我的搭档和另一名警官。
He killed my partner and another officer last night.
我该怎么办?
What can I do?
如果你跑，他会找到你的。
If you run, he'll find you.
——这是令人欣慰的。-这是事实。这个,呃…卡洛·加西亚完全是另一个级别的。
- That's comforting. - That's the truth. This, uh... This is Carlo Garcia is in a whole nother league.
你的体重超出了你的水平。
You're fighting out of your weight class.
我要揍死这混蛋。
I'm going to put a cap in this fucker.
你会害死自己的。
You're gonna get yourself killed.
好吧，我不能跑。
Well, I can't run.
我不能战斗。
I can't fight.
他们在局里有内应，所以我不能去自首。
They have someone inside the department, so I can't turn myself in.
看来我没有太多选择。
Doesn't look like I got a lot of options.
塑造你的战场，等待他来找你。
Shape your battlefield and wait till he comes for you.
这是出乎意料的。所以你要做好准备。
It will be unexpected. So you've got to be ready.
然后呢?
And then?
幸运的话，你会有机会的。
If you're lucky, you'll get your shot.
嗯,那是,呃…可怕的建议。
Hm, that's, uh... terrible advice.
我知道，但你不能去追魔鬼。
I know, but you don't go chasing the devil.
所以你搞砸了。现在你需要我的帮助。
So you fucked up. Now you need my help.
她有手机，我们有她的号码。
She has her cell, and we have her number.
我们只需要有人黑进去，找到她，卡洛，剩下的我来搞定。
All we need is someone to hack into it, track her down, Carlo, and I will take care of the rest.
没什么大不了的。
No big deal.
这是他的问题。
This is his problem.
我知道，但他是我的搭档。
I know, but he's my partner.
只有两个月。
Only for two months.
你觉得他会为你做同样的事吗?
You think he'd do the same thing for you?
我希望如此。
I would hope so.
我想以朋友的身份跟你说几句话。
I want to say something to you, and I mean this as a friend.
去吧,开枪。
Go ahead, shoot.
我担心你变得不可靠了。
I'm concerned that you've become unreliable.
这几天太难熬了。
It's been a rough couple days.
我们把这烂摊子收拾干净，然后就万事大吉了。
We'll clean this mess up, and then it's clear sailing.
没什么大不了的。
No big deal.
我想你需要休假。你变老了。
I think you need a vacation. You're getting old.
这两种说法都没错，但要对自己诚实。
Yeah, both of those are correct, but be honest with yourself.
你最近照镜子了吗?
You looked in the mirror lately?
我愿意用我的灵魂换回20岁。
I'd trade my soul to be 20 again.
你们俩在瞎扯些什么?
What are you two rambling on about?
青春浪费在年轻人身上。
That youth is wasted on the young.
不幸的是，经验浪费在那些不花时间享受生活的人身上。
And unfortunate that experience is wasted on those who don't take time to enjoy life.
阿诺德，我有很多事要做。我们今晚会回到这里。
Arnold, I have a lot to do. We'll be back here this evening.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
我打电话给我的人。他会和你保持联系的。
I'll call my guy. He'll be in touch.
对吧?
Alright?
照顾,加布。我们走吧。
Take care, Gabe. Let's go.
后来,老板。
Later, boss.
七种语言。
Seven languages.
作战行动的丝带。
Combat action ribbon.
枪支的讲师。
Firearms instructor.
侦探服务丝带。警察明星。
Detective Service ribbon. Police star.
天啊。
Geez.
4月2日。
April 2nd.
我是洛佩斯警官。
This is Officer Lopez.
-我找戴利。-他今天没来。
- I'm looking for Daley. - He hasn't come in today.
我负责他的工作。
I'm covering his desk.
-他在哪里?-女士，这不是…我是弗林警探。我要和他谈谈。
- Where is he? - Ma'am, that's not... This is Detective Flynn. I need to speak with him.
侦探弗林?
Detective Flynn?
我奉命奉劝你进来。
I'm under strict orders to advise you to come in.
该死的!
Damn it!
-很高兴见到你。-很高兴见到你。
- Good to see you. - Oh, nice to see you.
如果你们还需要什么，我非常乐意。
If you guys need anything else, I'd be more than happy.
经商还是旅游?
Business or pleasure?
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
你在想什么。
What you're thinking about.
好吧，两者都有一点。
Well, well, a little bit of both.
有趣的。
Intriguing.
嗯哼。是的。我在想盖比。
Mm-hmm. Yeah. I'm thinking about Gabe.
关于他的什么?
What about him?
老实说，他正在成为一个累赘。
Honestly, he's becoming a liability.
我不想打听你的事。
I don't want to pry into your business.
你知道的。
You know that.
但记住，盖比不只是为你工作。
But remember, Gabe doesn't just work for you.
他是你的朋友。
He's your friend.
所以才会这么难。
That's what makes it so hard.
嘿，搞什么鬼?
Hey, what the fuck?
嘿，你们在干什么?
Hey, what are you guys doing?
把枪给我。
Give me the fucking gun.
看着我，混蛋。
Look at me, motherfucker.
是吗?有什么事吗?
Yeah? What's up?
盖比，他们打中阿诺德了。
Gabe, they've hit Arnold.
——哦。-胳膊中了一枪，但他没事
- Oh. - Took one in the arm, but he's okay.
-谁负责?——拉方丹则。
- Who was on point? - LaFontaine.
阿诺德正在和他的妻子吃晚饭。
Arnold was having dinner with his wife.
他们把她弄得一团糟。
They made a mess of her.
-他们现在在哪里?-城市医疗中心
- Where they at now? - City medical center.
二楼。
Second floor.
他一直在找你。
He's been asking for you.
托米-怎么样?
How's Tomi?
她死在了手术台上。
She died on the operating table.
阿诺德会把事情闹大的。
Arnold is going to be raising hell.
作为官方律师，我强烈反对这种做法。
As official counsel, I must strongly advise against that course of action.
我们花了这么多年把这事变成了合法生意不能因为一种卑鄙的复仇欲望就放弃这一切。
We spent too many years turning this into a legitimate business to throw it all away over a base desire for revenge.
这么说古希腊人不相信以眼还眼，对吧?
So your ancient Greeks don't believe in an eye for an eye, huh?
事实上，他们称之为必要互惠。
Well, actually, they called it necessary reciprocity.
特洛伊战争结束后，奥德修斯回到伊萨卡，发现他的妻子佩内洛普不忠，他杀死了她所有的108名高贵的追求者，
When Odysseus returned to Ithaca after the Trojan War and found that his wife Penelope had been unfaithful, he murdered all 108 of her noble suitors,
然后他屠杀并肢解了自己的仆人因为他们允许这种轻率的行为发生。
and then he slaughtered and mutilated his own servants for allowing the indiscretions to happen.
听起来像一个把战争带回家的人。
Sounds like a man who brought his war home with him then.
他确实。每个人都为此付出了代价。
He did indeed. And everyone paid the price.
所以我离开。
So I'm leaving.
我是否回来取决于阿诺德的行动。
Whether or not I return will depend on Arnold's course of action.
但我对打仗没兴趣。
But I am not interested in fighting a war.
话虽如此，我认为我们不会再见面了。
Having said that, I don't think you and I will be seeing each other again.
我喜欢你，盖比。
I like you, Gabe.
不要陷入逆流。
Don't get caught in the undertow.
他们杀了她。
They killed her.
他们杀了我妻子。
They killed my wife.
——卡洛。——是吗?
- Carlo. - Yes?
明确这个房间。马上离开这里。
Clear this room. Get out of here now.
——好吧,每一个人。——走吧。照他说的做。
- Alright, everyone. - Let's go. Do as the man says.
离开这里，孩子们。不要动。
Get out of here, boys. Don't move.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
——老板……——闭嘴。不要说话。
- Boss... - Shut up. Don't talk.
你看到了吗?
You see that?
你他妈都干了些什么?
You see what you fuckin' did?
停止它!
Stop it!
给我滚出去。
Get the fuck out of here.
走吧!走了。
Go! Go.
把门关上!
Close the door!
卡洛,留下来。
Carlo, stay.
我想让他们受苦。
I want them to suffer.
别担心，宝贝。他们会。
Don't you worry, baby. They will.
首先，你需要休息。
First, you're going to need some rest.
-只要他们还活着就不会。-不会太久的。
- Not if they're still breathing. - They won't be for long.
我们上战场，你得想清楚，好吗?
We go to war, we need you thinking clearly, alright?
风险太大了。
Stakes are way too high.
你是对的。
You're right.
你总是对的。
You're always right.
我要在这里待一段时间。
I'm gonna stay here for a while.
尽你所能去查。
Go find out what you can.
回头见，伙计，好吗?
I'll see you later, man, okay?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我爱她。
I loved her.
她也爱你。
She loved you, too.
对不起,兄弟。
I'm sorry, brother.
我真的很爱她。
I really loved her.
我知道。
I know.
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
射手是专业人士。不是这里的人。
Shooters were professionals. Not from around here.
他们用的是什么枪?
What kind of gun they use?
在墨西哥，它被称为cuerno de chivo，因为这本杂志看起来像山羊的角。
In Mexico, it's known as a cuerno de chivo because the magazine looks like a goat's horn.
他们就是喜欢它，他们肯定会用它来表达自己的观点。
They just love it, and they definitely use it to make a statement.
要我说，钱都押在哥伦比亚墨西哥人身上了。
If you asked me, the money is on the Colombian Mexican.
那就是跟委拉斯开兹有关的人。
Someone tied to Velasquez then.
也可能是故意这么看的。
Or made to look that way.
噢,是吗?你猜是谁?
Oh, yeah? Who do you figure?
有弗莱迪的消息吗?
Have we heard from Vlady?
我不知道，老大。他有什么动机?
I don't know, boss. What motive would he have?
我让开。
Me out of the way.
这样事情就简单多了，不是吗?
Makes things a lot easier, doesn't it?
如果我们继续对付弗莱迪，福利特会生气的。
Follett's gonna be pissed if we move on Vlady.
这是肯定的。
That's for damn sure.
操他!
Fuck him!
我会搞定那个狗娘养的。
I'll handle that son of a bitch.
这是我的电话。
It's my call.
你确定吗?
You sure about this?
你该死的正确。
You're goddamn right.
他们杀了我妻子!
They killed my wife!
我们在说她!
We're talking about her!
很好。你明白了。
Fine. You got it.
它会完成。
It'll get done.
这次袭击一定是为了报复委拉斯开兹。
The hit had to be retaliation for Velasquez.
弗莱迪没有动机。
Vlady has no motive.
我告诉你，阿诺德疯了。
I'm telling you, Arnold's losing it.
这是一个错误。
This is a mistake.
你不会因为生气就打俄罗斯黑帮。
You don't just hit a Russian mobster 'cause you're pissed.
找到那个女孩了。她在泰瑞斯汽车旅馆。
Got a hit on the girl. She's at the Terrace Motel.
太好了。处理好这件事，然后我来解决她。
Great. Deal with this, then I'll finish her off.
的问题。看。
Question. Look.
我想把它藏在前面。
I'm trying to hide it in the front.
看起来像个大肥鸡巴，所以我就…我不…我不知道该怎么办。
Looks like a big fat dick, so I just... I don't... I don't know what to do.
你怎么把枪和相机藏起来的?
How do you hide a gun with a camera?
你是怎么做到的?
How do you do it?
振作起来,伙计。
Buck up, man.
什么?
What?
♬♬夕阳的声音
♪ The sounds of sundown ♪
♬把骷髅翻过来♬
♪ Turn the skeleton inside out ♪
♬并发出不熟悉的声音
♪ And make the unfamiliar sound ♪
♬你知道你差一点就会洒出来
♪ You know just how close you came to spilling ♪
♬你的血管里没有血
♪ No blood inside your veins ♪
有件事你应该知道，♬
♪ There's something you should know ♪
♪关于风♪
♪ About the wind ♪
♬它会朝哪个方向吹
♪ And which way it will blow ♪
就算他知道，你也知道
♪ Even though he knows, you know ♪
♪死神害怕去的地方♪
♪ Where the reaper fears to go ♪
嘿，嘿，大麦克。
Hey, hey, Big Mike.
我要去见弗莱迪了?
I'm gonna head up to see Vlady, huh?
怎么了,伙计?
What's up, man?
那个俄国人怎么样了?
How's the Russian doing?
他在那里对每个人大喊大叫，压力太大了。
He up there yelling at everybody, stressed out.
天啊。有什么新鲜事吗?
Geez. What's new?
帮我盯着这家伙，好吗?
Hey, keep an eye on this guy for me, huh?
我还坐在孩子们的桌子上?
And I'm still here at the kids table, huh?
他们也不让你听大人说话，对吧?
They don't let you listen to the grown-ups talk either, huh?
-这就是不尊重。-是的。
- Disrespectful is what it is. - Yeah.
哇,哇。嘿,嘿。不,不,不。
Whoa, whoa. Hey, hey. No, no, no.
严格的命令，禁止访客。
Strict orders, no visitors.
阿诺德称为Vlady。我有他的快递。
Arnold called Vlady. I have a delivery for him.
-你别进去，盖比。-你为什么这么说?
- Don't you go in there, Gabe. - Why do you say that?
我有个约会。我正在付款。
I have an appointment. I am making a payment.
-我才不管呢。听着，我有个约会。
- I don't give a fuck. - Look, I have an appointment.
这是信封。
Here is the envelope.
听着，弗莱蒂打俄罗斯电话，但我打美国电话因为他英语说得不好。
Listen, Vlady makes his Russian calls, but I make all his American calls on the accountability that he does not speak great English.
你在撒谎,伙计。
You're lying, dude.
我不知道，伙计。也许他们互相发过短信。
I don't know, man. Maybe they texted each other.
但不是我死就是你亡。
But it's going to be me or you.
不管怎样，他都得拿到钱。
Either way, he's going to have to get it.
你想拿给他吗?
You want to take it to him?
去做吧。对不起,加布。
Go ahead. I'm sorry, Gabe.
谢谢你,兄弟。
Thank you, brother.
这是紧张的。他快疯了。我很抱歉。
It's been tense. He's fucking losing his mind. I'm sorry.
啊!
Ah!
你应该直接杀了他。
You should have just shot him.
厨房。
Kitchen.
-再说一遍。-我们为什么要烧这里?
- Tell me again. - Why are we burning this place?
这叫做发送信息。
It's called sending a message.
-搞定了吗?-你看当地新闻了吗?
- Is it done? - You watching the local news?
-这次没有目击者吗?——没有。
- No witnesses this time? - No.
好。他们会怪罪墨西哥人。
Good. They'll blame the Mexicans.
你是说你会怪墨西哥人?
You mean you'll blame the Mexicans?
你这态度是怎么回事?
What's with the attitude?
我们无缘无故就捅了马蜂窝。
We just kicked a hornet's nest for no good reason.
-我下的命令。-这就是你需要的理由。
- I gave the order. - That's all the reason you need.
那个该死的警探是怎么回事?
What's the deal with the fucking detective?
你答应过我的。所以好好照顾她。
You gave me your word. So take care of her.
——我会的。-别告诉我。
- I will. - Don't tell me.
给我看。
Show me.
我告诉你。他正在失去它。
I'm telling you. He's losing it.
让我上车。
Drop me at my car.
反正我得去洗个澡。
Got to take a shower anyways.
我全身都是埃斯特班的血。
I'm all fucking covered in Esteban.
一场夜总会大火烧焦的废墟中发现了一名夜总会老板和他的三名员工的尸体。
Bodies of a nightclub owner and three of his staff were discovered in the charred remains of a property fire.
昨天，两起大胆的卡特尔式杀人事件震撼了这座城市，枪手向杰克逊的一家餐厅开火。
A pair of audacious cartel style killings rocked the city yesterday when gunmen opened fire on a restaurant in Jackson.
其中一名受害者已被确认为Tomi Solomon，当地房地产巨头Arnold Solomon的妻子，长期以来被怀疑与有组织犯罪有关联。
One of the shooting victims has been identified as Tomi Solomon, wife of local real estate magnate Arnold Solomon, who's long been suspected of having ties to organized crime.
所罗门,看到…你是在比赛之后去的。
Solomon, seen here... You went after the competition.
但竞争对手进行了反击。
But the competition hit back.
——加布。—留言。
- Gabe here. - Leave a message.
——嘿,加布。-你他妈的在哪儿?
- Hey, Gabe. - Where the fuck are you?
这是我第三次打电话了。
This is the third time I've called.
我们在汽车旅馆等你。
We're here at the motel waiting for you.
不管你在不在，这事都会发生。
This is going down whether you're here or not.
盖比没有回答。让我们滚。
No answer from Gabe. Let's roll.
你都想要，对吧，混蛋。
You want it all, don't you, bastard.
快趴在地上!
On the floor quick!
这他妈的是怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on out here?
他妈的。
Fuck.
进入!
Get in!
去你妈的!
Fuck you!
上车，不然你就死定了!
Get in or you're dead!
来吧!
Come on!
是的,去吧。
Yeah, go ahead.
你他妈在干什么，盖比?
What the fuck are you doing, Gabe?
你疯了吗?
Have you lost your mind?
你不明白，伙计。
You don't understand, man.
别他妈废话了。
Quit the fucking bullshit right now.
把她带回来。你在玩弄我的生命。
Just bring her back. You're playing with my life.
不可能发生的。
Ain't gonna happen.
你知道现在发生了什么吗?
You know what happens now?
我写了这本书。
I wrote the book.
你他妈想怎么做就怎么做。
You do what the fuck you go to do.
系上安全带。
Put your safety belt on.
去做吧。
Go ahead.
这他妈的是怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on?
我完成了,老兄。
I'm done, man.
我要辞职了，先生。
I'm tendering my resignation, sir.
我说你辞职，你就辞职。
You quit when I say you quit.
现在，那个女孩在哪里?
Now, where's the girl?
-她和我在一起。-那是她住的地方
- She's with me. - That's where she staying.
如果你够聪明，就放我们两个走。
If you're smart, you'll let us both go.
你觉得我会让她离开吗?
You think I'm going to let her walk away?
听着,男人。
Listen, man.
艾丽克丝死的时候你和我在一起，对吧?
You were with me when Alex died, right?
托米已经死了。
Tomi is dead now.
是你说的吗，你个混蛋?
You bring that up, you piece of shit?
别让它毁了你的生活，朋友。
Don't let it ruin your life, my friend.
我会抓到你的。
I'm going to hunt you down.
别做你做不到的承诺，好吗?
Don't make promises you can't keep, okay?
你知道这意味着什么。
You know what this means.
祝你晚上愉快。
Have a good night.
把那个混蛋的头给我拿来。
Bring me that bastard's head.
让我带你进去。
Let me bring you in.
你可以策反所罗门。
You can turn state against Solomon.
我作证之前我们都已经死了。
We'd both be dead before I could testify.
那个人，卡洛·加西亚，是你的搭档吗?
That guy, Carlo Garcia, he your partner?
是的,他是。
Yeah, he was.
如果我们够幸运，他会离我们越远越好。
If we're lucky, he'll put as much distance between us as he can.
我最近运气很好。
I had lots of luck lately.
所有这些都很糟糕。
All of it bad.
哦,放松。还能更糟吗?
Oh, relax. How much worse can it get?
我有预感我会查出来的。
I've got a feeling I'm gonna find out.
放松。
Relax.
坐下来。
Sit down.
我们都可以用这个。
We can both use this.
这是你妻子吗?
Is this your wife?
是的。是的。
Yes. Yes.
她通过了。
She passed.
嗯哼。
Mm-hmm.
你没事吧?
You okay?
听着，你为所罗门工作了这么多年。
Look, you've worked for Solomon for years.
你可以把我送回旅馆的。
You could have dropped me back at the motel.
现在我们在喝酒。
Now we're having drinks.
为什么?
Why?
我向某人许下了承诺。
I made someone a promise.
亚历克斯。
Alex.
她想让我离开这种生活。
She wanted me out of this life.
离开这里，逃到非洲去。
Get away, escape to Africa.
好好利用我的经验，保护大象。
Put my experience to good use, protect the elephants.
打一场精彩的仗。
Fight the good fight.
她发现自己得了癌症。
She discovered she had cancer.
她走后，我迷失了方向。
After she was gone, I was lost.
我只剩下阿诺德了。
Arnold was all I had left.
你妻子的事我很遗憾。
I'm sorry about your wife.
我很感激你让我活了下来。
And I'm thankful you let me live.
但你还是黑帮战士，我还是警察。
But you're still a mob soldier, and I'm still a cop.
恐怕我所做的只是推迟了不可避免的事情。
Yeah, well, I'm afraid all I've done is delayed the inevitable.
我们今晚都可能会死。
We're both probably going to die tonight.
那你的计划是什么?
So what's your plan, then?
怎么，喝一杯，把悲伤淹没，然后等它们来召唤你吗?
What, have a drink, drown your sorrows, and wait for them to come calling?
是的，差不多，是的。
Yeah, well, pretty much, yeah.
我建造了这个地方，设计了它。
I built this place, designed it.
墙壁，家具。
The walls, the furniture.
所有东西都加固了，而且防火。
Everything's reinforced and fireproof.
亚历克斯的浴室实际上就是个密室。
And Alex's bathroom is a de facto panic room.
这是一个堡垒。
It's a fortress.
你有陷阱吗?
You got booby traps?
我有枪。
I've got guns.
——这是吗?-很多枪。
- That's all? - A lot of guns.
我知道怎么用。
And I know how to use them.
另外，那些人要来找我。
Plus, those guys are coming to me.
有主场优势。
Got home field advantage.
我杀过比这更便宜的人。
I've killed people for a lot less.
是的。你有，是吗?
Yeah. You have, haven't you?
是的,我有。
Yes, I have.
准备迎接客人吧，好吗?
Let's get ready for our guests, shall we?
他们马上就到。
They'll be here soon.
只有被炮弹直接击中才能破坏这个房间。
Nothing short of a direct hit from an artillery round will breach this room.
如果情况不妙，他们会的，锁上门，躺在浴缸里。
If things go south, and they will, lock the door and lay in the tub.
躲藏不是我的风格。
Hiding is not my style.
有时这就是生与死的区别。
Sometimes it's a difference between living and dying.
如果出事了，我知道去哪找你。
Well, if shit hits the fan, I know where to find you.
嗯。
Hm.
在浴缸里。
In the tub.
适时指出。
Duly noted.
我不知道发生了什么。
I don't know what happened.
我是说，那个该死的警察。
I mean, that fucking cop.
把他们都处理掉。无论付出多大的代价。
Just get rid of them both. Whatever the cost.
都有?
Both?
但他是我的搭档。
But he's my partner.
他是我的老朋友之一。
He's one of my oldest friends.
我别无选择。
I got no choice.
我是说，这值得吗?
I mean, is this even worth it?
适者生存。
Survival of the fittest.
当盖比带我来的时候，我就知道总有一天当你有事情需要处理的时候会找我。
When Gabe brought me on, I knew there'd be a day when I'd be the one you'd call when things needed to be taken care of.
他做出了自己的选择。
He made his choice.
现在你做你的。
Now you make yours.
没问题，老大。
You got it, boss.
一群表情严肃的混蛋。
A bunch of serious looking assholes.
还有个长着色情明星胡子的男人。
And a guy with a porn star mustache.
拉方丹则。
LaFontaine.
快开门，盖比!
Open the damn door, Gabe!
他危险吗?
He dangerous?
也许可以用更好的除臭剂。
Could use a better deodorant maybe.
来吧。
Come on.
我没时间跟你扯淡。
I ain't got time for this horseshit.
没有我的命令，谁都不许行动。
Don't nobody do nothing unless I say.
盖比，我要把那个女警察还给所罗门先生。
Gabe, I'm taking that lady cop back to Mr. Solomon.
不管你同意与否。
With or without your consent.
就这样，是吗?
Just like that, huh?
是的。
Yep.
那么，会是什么呢?
So, what's it gonna be?
让我理理头绪。
So let me get this straight.
我让你带走她，我就自由了。
I let you take her, I go free.
当然,加布。
Sure, Gabe.
看在过去的份上。
For old times' sake.
好吧。
Okay.
听起来很划算。
Sounds like a good deal.
看在过去的份上。
For old times' sake.
你搞砸了，盖比。
You done fucked up now, Gabe.
也许。
Perhaps.
他们需要一段时间重新集结，但他们会回来的。
It'll take them a while to regroup, but they'll be back.
你有一段时间过得很好，不是吗?
You had it good for a while, didn't you?
汽车，乡下的大房子。
Cars, big house in the country.
很多钱可以拯救很多大象。
Plenty of money to save lots of elephants.
我猜你妻子不知道这一切的真正来源直到她知道。
I'm guessing your wife never knew where it all really came from until she did.
这时你必须做出承诺。
And that's when you had to make your promise.
嫉妒?
Jealous?
我知道我把坏人都抓起来了，所以我睡得很香。
I sleep soundly knowing I put away the bad guys.
我想没有比问心无愧更柔软的枕头了。
Well, I guess there's no softer pillow than a clear conscience.
有一次，在东区卖冰毒。
One time, a meth dealer on the east side.
我们执行了搜查令，凌晨四点踹开了他的门。
We served a warrant and kicked in his door at 4:00 a.m.
他有三个孩子。女儿。
He had three kids. Daughters.
他让他们做的事。
What he made them do.
父母应该保护他们的孩子。
Parents are supposed to protect their children.
我向他逼近。
I drew down on him.
那里的军官不会开口的。
Not an officer there would have talked.
那你最后做了什么?
So, what did you end up doing?
我打电话给CPS逮捕了他。
I called CPS and arrested him.
我相信法律，加布里埃尔。
I believe in the law, Gabriel.
我想这就是为什么你比我优秀。
I guess that's why you're a better person than me.
就像我的Alex一样。
Just like my Alex.
我们在等的人，他有多厉害?
The guy we're waiting for, how good is he?
他觉得他跟我一样厉害。
He thinks he's as good as I am.
他是年轻的。
He is younger.
不是很让人放心。
Not very reassuring.
是啊，但这不是命中注定的。
Yeah, well, it wasn't meant to be.
如果他比你强怎么办?
What if he's better than you?
洗浴时间。
Bath time.
因为下一个就是你。
Because you'll be next.
介意我进来吗?
Mind if I come in?
我让他跟你谈五分钟。
I've asked him for five minutes to talk to you.
你欠我的。
You owe me that.
来吧。
Come on.
我得到了它。
I got it.
有人说这都是女人的错。
Some people claim there's a woman to blame.
但是我知道... ...这是我自己的错。
But I know... ... it's my own damn fault.
惹了很多麻烦，小姐。
Caused a lot of trouble, senorita.
你确定要这样吗?
You sure you want this?
木已成舟。
What's done is done.
在那些家伙冲进来之前我们还有五分钟。
We have five minutes before those guys come storming up in here.
前特工枪手，SX承包商。
Ex-agency shooters, SX contractors.
你知道的，真正的。
You know, the real deal.
我相信你会标记其中一些，但他们会完成任务的。
I'm sure you'll tag some of them, but they'll get the job done.
你为什么要这么做?
Why are you doing this?
她没有人!
She's no one!
伙计，别逼我杀了你。
Man, don't make me kill you.
你的假设太多了。
You're assuming a lot.
就像他妈的西部片，对吧?
Like a fucking western, huh?
就像他妈的西部片。
Like a fucking western.
爱死它了。
Love it.
我比你年轻多了。
I'm much younger than you.
快得多。
Much faster.
最好还是确定一下。
Better looking for sure.
我是无情的。
I'm ruthless.
我可以瞬间杀了你。
I can kill you in a heartbeat.
这是多么的浪费。
What a waste.
它的时间。
It's time.
所罗门给你的钱不够!
Solomon's not paying you enough!
回家!活下去，改日再战。
Go home! Live to fight another day.
你们这些混蛋谁想走，我就亲手杀了你们。
Any of you fuckers want to leave, I'll kill you myself.
我们的任务就是干掉这个混蛋!
Our mission is to take this motherfucker out!
你们谁也拿不到钱…
None of you get paid...
我去。
I'll go.
我可以守住车道。
I can cover the driveway.
走吧!去吧!
Go! Go ahead!
走吧!走吧!走吧!
Go! Go! Go!
啊!
Ah!
我记得你说过这房子是坚不可摧的。
I thought you said this house was impenetrable.
嗯，我也这么认为。
Well, I thought so, too.
我是个合同工杀手，不是合同工?
I'm a contractor killer, not a contract builder, okay?
这看起来不太好。
This doesn't look good.
来吧!现在就拿出来!
Come on! Take that out now!
我该出去透透气了。
Time for me to get some fresh air.
洗浴时间。
Bath time.
那就这样吧。
There you go.
保持水分。
Stay hydrated.
——在这里!-在卡车后面。
- Over here! - Behind the truck.
啊!
Aaah!
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
为我工作的人一定有暴力倾向。
Men that work for me must be capable of violence.
同时也要明白威胁的威力。
And also understand the power of a well-placed threat.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
海军陆战队吗?
Marine Corps?
海军。海豹突击队4。
Navy. SEAL Team 4.
我需要新的枪手。
I need new shooters.
我的上一个男人已经离开了。
My last guy moved on.
不会让你失望的。
Won't let you down.
这是路易斯·委拉斯开兹的。
This is for Luis Velasquez.
帮我个忙。
Do me a favor.
帮我处理好这件事。
Take care of this for me.
当然，我会的。
Sure, I'll do that.
嘿。
Hey.
我支持你。
I got your back.
你好的,加布?
You alright, Gabe?
是的，伙计，我很好。
Yeah, man, I'm good.
——你明白吗?-很好，很好。
- You okay? - All good, all good.
来吧,伙计们。让我们完成它。
Come on, guys. Let's get it done.
♪我忍不住要保留这个念头
♪ I can't help but keep the notion ♪
♪我不知道什么对我好
♪ I don't know what's good for me ♪
♪当我只知道怎么撒谎♪
♪ When all I'd ever learned is how to lie ♪
嗯，隐藏的是智慧的手
♪ Well, the hidden hands of wisdom ♪
♬保留所有可以保留的♬
♪ Holds all that it can keep ♪
♪我所知道的只是我的时间里的烦恼
♪ And all I know is the trouble in my time ♪
♬我不翻石头
♪ Well, I don't turn over stones ♪
♪那里除了我什么都没有
♪ There wasn't nothing there but me ♪
所以我又往下挖了一点，只为找到♬
♪ So I dug a little deeper just to find ♪
♪高高的挂在树上的不是一个懒人
♪ That it ain't a lazy man who hangs high upon the tree ♪
♬他只知道他那个时代的麻烦
♪ And all he knew he was the trouble in his time ♪
♪我坐回去听♪
♪ I sit right back and listen ♪
这里再重复一次♬
♪ This here bears to repeat ♪
♬谁用手指着谁就握着火
♪ Well, he who points the finger holds the fire ♪
他把自己藏在后面
♪ And he hides himself asunder ♪
♬从水瓶座晚上♬
♪ From Aquarius at night ♪
但他只知道他的时间里有麻烦
♪ But all he knows is trouble in his time ♪
♬每次你想喝酒的时候
♪ Every time you get to drinking ♪
♬你大声谈论你的梦想♬
♪ You talk loud about your dreams ♪
♬你把它们像旗帜一样挂在一条线上
♪ And you hoist them up like flags upon a line ♪
♬跑上愤怒的针♬
♪ Run up the angry needle ♪
♬越高越好
♪ Get as high as high can be ♪
♪因为你所知道的只是你的时间里的麻烦
♪ 'Cause all you know is trouble in your time ♪
♪我在寻找目的地♪
♪ Well, I searched for destination ♪
♬她在那里惩罚我
♪ There she was chastising me ♪
♬她选的那些词是想让我变得憔悴
♪ And the words she chose were meant to make me pine ♪
嗯，她说去见那个女孩
♪ Well, she said go see the girl ♪
♪用来缝你的旧黑链♪
♪ That used to sew your old black chains ♪